I think so yeah oh so let me get in this
so I can wait hang on
wait I'm trying to alt-tab away from
this so I can mute my oh I'm dying
oh you pseudo killed me oh hang on
no I fullscreen dat before and then I
couldn't switch away all right well my
name is rock dude 69 I so let's go
fullscreen okay yeah yeah
is that gonna work I don't know that
doesn't work at all
wait we're gonna set the resolution
right okay I do know about computers I
may not know about legal legends but the
other alternative was live streaming
trying to get tensorflow GPU to compile
so oh yeah I look I'm beating them
beating them up yeah look at that I got
his gold yeah that's right
this right box take that oh no if they
have a turret how'd they build that oh
yeah yeah yeah beat up the turret yeah
oh yeah die now let's attack the enemy
crystal shit yeah crystal shit wait
just try to put my streamer headphones
on - oh no I can't go there can't go
there I'm dying alright alpha-strike
is this good oh yeah wait let's
alpha-strike the turret can I do that no
no no
oh yeah meditate yeah was that good oh
now I can use our yeah I beat the turret
up
oh yeah I win get come along greeter
working on stream bro all right yeah
she's pretty
look but like at a chair I got a gaming
chair how can I be bad at gaming
you know what I found out all these
games they don't even you can't even pay
more money to win you can only buy skins
I was amazed when I found this out
learning a basic ability Oh make it rain
yeah it's gonna be a hot key for that oh
I'm always mid always mid yeah
I played this game I favor played one
game of this before
earn experience but I can't go there
can I kill snipe from my minions and
gain experience that way
oh the enemy hero oh yeah yeah take that
Annie
wait so how do i I don't have to click
there
do I have to click
yeah see how I lured them away from the
turret I'm so good at this game my
minions will tank for me
I know I know terms structures are
immune to most spells okay
well that's good to know these up
I like make it rain oh yeah make it rain
better yeah perfect
oh yeah yeah kill the hero kill Annie
kill Annie the turrets targeting me oh
yeah get her all right I want to heal
perfect me lovely oh my bad friend help
me out what a pro did I do that
Oh buy items oh good point do I have to
go back here can I just click Harold we
have to go back to the start to buy
items oh no it's not what I wanted yo
should we hack legal legends instead
they want me to hack legal legends
instead of my twitchy's cuz I'm not very
good at it it was the shop is this the
shop I see you orb oh the furry thing oh
sweet
what do I want AB dagger that sounds
good buy more dagger bye that probably
wasn't a good buy zeal oh that's bye
Plus
craft epic items oh I understand
I don't I lied let's go mid always MIT
can I hold control to run oh press B to
come back to base
Oh recall yeah no I know this I've seen
that in streams before oh yeah die
that's right yeah that's right that's
right rock dude 69 always better make it
rain I love this game
this is the best cuz they she make rain
unlock the camera press why wait my
letters daughter I don't have keyboards
own letters on my keyboard I don't think
that works for me I tried that button
yeah Annie you didn't buy items did you
someone stole my kill it's best so that
looks pretty cool
come on your home be I feel it a still
but now I got an XY why does that do
this unable to purchase
who's attacking my target down here
always MIT because you can just buy one
boot I understand I understand I'm just
gonna get a lot of them
oh yeah wait these are just BOTS I'm not
even playing a real game I shouldn't
feel good about myself
wait let's just end this what am i doing
let's kill them all right bye turret
alright let's rush their Nexus let's go
no no it's not good I think maybe oh
straw all yeah I can't make it rain on
the structure it doesn't work yes my
first bot game why do I have to play
more oh but I'm already so good what if
I just win this one
that's right killing spree I'm a great
League Legends player alright alright I
understand the towers heart die
oh yeah wait this crystal thing he
doesn't even attack back today we had a
crystal thinking to accept our crystal
thing he wasn't blown up all we get
super minions
I've watched League of Legends streams
before
I'm really good this game guys oh no no
no I'm really bad a fortnight oh I could
try to play fortnight but I'm really bad
but like it's not even funny I just lose
victory Oh 5v5 blind tech okay how do my
friend you complete all tutorial games
oh I have to do this one too I bought
items from the store last game yeah I
know yeah some guy on Twitch told me I
had to buy items alright let's just win
really fast I'm now good at this game so
I can win really fast nope no way I'm
rock dude 69 other people take a deal
hot on stuff yeah all the time
wait no what happened to make it rain I
like to make it rain
no I used to have different abilities
why did my abilities change there's a
new champion
I don't like I picked our though but I
like the other one better why didn't
nobody tell me this oh thank you I
wasn't even asking for a Dorito oh I
didn't know you were gesturing I was
talking about the complexity of my oh
she does backflips
I picked her cuz she looked pretty now
do they all do hmm
alright the by item I want McNuggets No
oh yeah I'll buy one of those wait I
spent all my money on a book wait you
subscribe for three months nano danger 7
thank you so much I love when they
subscribe you don't understand how I
made $135 streaming on twitch wait all
right so I got I bought a book is that
good
wait why did I pick a complicated
champion
Oh deal the killing blow to 12 minions
all that sounds easy
she's terrible his woman's terrible oh
my god that's what they all say
boo charming I'll be charming oh that
was good
oh I see it makes those fireballs Oh
control Q I see Thank You max Q okay you
guys think I should vote for Q we'll ask
them twitch max you wait is Q actually
good how do you know all the champions
why did I pick a gobbler get a champion
you should send George don't pick that
one it's complicated they do I had a
choice of five champions and I picked
wrong I don't have any cute
how many minions have I delivered the
killing blow to control queue oh yeah I
have Q now I think I missed them I fired
off my queue when I missed ya minion you
charmed
I'll Q's the best oh we should add queue
before oq just slays everything me just
use the level 1
no these bots suck do they even know how
to buy items now we have more queue I
got to go home guys
but I can buy things with all my money
twitch and cam girls is very similar oh
look I bought all of those now let it
buy this and now can i buy that not a
lot of money new Tom Cruise is great to
have you watching my channel 20 there's
20 people out there watching me play
League of Legends imagine all the people
who are actually good at this game we
would love to have 20 people watching
them oh yeah yeah I killed them yeah no
no they killing me uh retreat retreat
retreat Retreat retreat oh no I died
yeah why try to avoid dying enemies get
stronger with each death I wasn't paying
attention and they ganged up on me I was
talking about how excited I was to have
20 viewers I miss my old hero that could
make it rain do you know which one can
make it rain can I spend real money on
huh wait how much that's so worth it
wait wait so they give you a trial with
the expensive one I thought you couldn't
pay to win I thought you couldn't pay to
win
they're not equally balanced this
woman's terrible that's what they all
say but I don't believe it
oh no you killed my ally all right
that's it that's it I can take these
guys oh yeah look at this triple kill
yeah yeah that's right BOTS oh I got a
retreat I wish I had make it rain
oh I didn't make it rain I would win
wait ten real dollars can I get it if I
like play good instead I want on locker
with experience D to run faster waited
no way oh it's my way it's like my
ability or something oh no run run run
that's right yeah you want to engage now
that's right
killing spree
oh I understand how this orb thing works
now yeah I say this is complicated I
like to make it rain wait if I pay ten
real dollars I have to vote my credit
card out don't I can I pay with Bitcoin
yeah how could I type in my credit card
on stream i can't I can't upgrade my
queue anymore I could pay with PayPal
what if I get a lot of in-game gold is
that good enough
how much
and I really want the hero that I know
how to use cuz she was easy to make it
use start with your e this guy's saying
to use my e
yeah he was make it rain on the good
hero no I know the enemies a buck but
we're gonna play a real we're gonna play
real opponents very soon I promise guys
they make you play two games against
bots and the bots are beating me but I
believe in me oh yeah look I charmed
this one is that good die die die die
die yeah unstoppable that's right
or I gotta finish killing these BOTS
first don't worry I got a double kill
I'm really good at this game
put your fill in the middle of the map
I'm button spamming yeah yeah yeah no
that's fine we're going we're gonna push
look it look I got all these minions
we're gonna push nice I'm saying
oh yeah Morgana yeah get charmed that's
right I learned how to use this hero
I'll level up that's right godlike
George I'm godlike oh so you always need
to level or whenever available or is
always a better ability than all the
other ones wait really
yeah Suze called your ultimate ability
guys is that really true
a tank on your arm man
uh-oh I miss make it rain
that was a good ability died no no no
run run run oh how do I run fast D I
love D really when someone tell me this
digit or L didn't tell me anything can I
use B often
ah I forgot to take my R again
ooh that looks good
whoo that looks really good let's get
that one all right wait let's end this
game so we can play real players and
then we'll play for tonight afterward I
League of Legends no I'm good at this
game now don't worry but you know how to
play this game hey guys no no no no stop
stop stop push no don't let don't kill
my ally I meant single-handedly take you
guys all on don't worry I'm rock dude 69
that's right legendary yeah look at that
I know it's on this game is stupid I'm
playing box
ah I have are now
oh you're lucky I missed dude
go home go home go home go home go home
go home no no no oh wow that was close
you're our is-3 - what does that mean oh
I can't hit it three times
oh but I can't use my art right now it's
not ready I can only use it once every
minute but I can use it three times
quickly but if I don't use it quickly I
understand all right
these minions won't even know what hit
them
no I charmed a minion by accident I want
to charm that hero more are yes I'm
gonna get to use our again
all right
Facebook graded this game for point 1
out of 5 I missed
oh I have my are back
I have to go all the way home to heal
this takes forever
don't recall okay don't worry I wasn't
going to I was just thinking about it
but then I remember that I have an our
ability and I'm indestructible except
I'm not I'm gonna die
slayed my ally
oh I thought that they would heal me if
I went into their base it only heals
when you go to your base that was a scam
okay
ah this games hard you guys know I'm
walking across the map it takes a long
time
what do I have - is that what my are
ability does oh man no these people are
gonna know what hit him because I have
an AR ability
ar AR AR AR AR AR AR
yeah victory yeah let's play
you have a rock dude wait Rock 269
alright good okay how can i buy that
here oh that's good that's too hard
will you buy points there perhaps
thousand yeah you can buy it now oh
really
yeah can I sell my voice for ten real
dollars no oh wait we're so where is
that here oh you have to go to shop
which is the coins I get how good and
then champion so what's her name miss
fortune 200 just search and she's make
it rain girl yeah
oh wow I can I have 6,000 bees but for
me you also said 6,000 but then turn
that turn to 3000 hey it's a bug I think
yeah 3000 how do I earn more you earn
more we can
can I earn 150 really quickly I think so
all right let's play well do you have my
friend Lucas friend requests oh great
perfect all right yeah we're gonna play
League of Legends where's the weed
here's the wheat guys but it's a work
night so we're not smoking weed here's
gum detoxify toothpaste wait I don't
need open capsule whoa oh oh whoa they
know something where's capsule I will
hack server but later profile maybe is
when I arrive like items somewhere
collection icons
given to players who choose all your
Tony I could have chosen misfortune is
that near stole loot
no I already did this I think so where
do you say I do this no no no no no no
we don't hack shit anymore cuz I'm
retired you guys could sit could you
gift me money could you give me a
hundred fifty shits why not oh I have to
be level one or above to receive a gift
perfect I'm level three yeah just go to
click on loot and go to the gifting
Center and then type in my name in loot
oh I can sell all I can sell I can sell
the terrible hero who seduced me with
our good looks Sal Kate I don't have her
yeah yeah just go to just go to the
coins and then go to gift disenchant
into essence by Kate oh so much essence
she is beautiful I know but she's
apparently very complex you can't give
me blue stuff
can i buy champion now I have money now
I'm gonna buy a champion now by
misfortune okay good bye oh I was only
50 away Kate won Kate one day this is my
promise to you I will buy you back um
thank you to major
she was looks like Thai so left I'm
terribly sorry for what I said
I feel bad one day just like Liam Neeson
and taken I'll come back alright wait
I'm joining your game wait I hear your
voice on here alright I don't know what
should we play
you picked Kate as well oh can you buy
new icons
I have $22,000 can I find your buddy
all right yeah I turned off your voice
already all right you're the owner of
the party begin matchmaking let's go
let's play some League of Legends well
you got to play the other game pack
go twitchy's I want nuggets but let's
see how much I weigh too much for
Nuggets oh I love this game
you guys you can't play a ram don't
worry I wasn't wait we plan you can't
play a ram you need more champs I think
nota major knows a lot about this game
oh except let's go
how much do you have high place care so
much I got a date Friday night I'm very
excited you guys very excited thank our
fire facility
I already clicked accept all right so
how do I play oh I know which one I want
misfortune let's go
no it's not a man it's a woman a date no
it's not Taylor Swift no no I don't know
I think I'd actually be overwhelmed that
intimidated and wouldn't be able to do
well on a date with Taylor Swift
but Talulah Riley on the other hand
anyone else having audio problems no
it's not tender you guys this is
authentic fire festival merchandise and
swear man who's duel eepa she's not
Caitlyn my sold and disenchanted into
essence that's devastating
it's like scobie's but less serious
switches I will try plate get a csgo
free to play I'll try playing csgo I'll
follow you better at it than fortnight
at least I know I never to be the sniper
I now to hang out on the roof for snipe
people no no no Selena Gomez the one
with the donut ooh is that Ariana Grande
dials go I'm ready I'm not to play this
game we're gonna top but I always go mid
let's go top I'm with you I'm with you
I like dumb Abed anymore I have a
mattress on the floor I live in a closet
I'm off my twitch streams lagging
hmm almost bad time
how many FPS the way yeah I have an
external GPU box with an NVIDIA GPU but
not using it because my monitor doesn't
support it but one day we're gonna
livestream trying to compile tensor flow
with GPU support for Mac what time is
that let's say 12:30 late
yes
mastery I was a shitty computer this is
what
wait but this is taking too long
cooee boot him
tweet-tweet boot Oh bro bro you poor
[Music]
I already haven't played a game of
League Legends yet and I'm already tired
not if shitty Wi-Fi is the real problem
we have we have gigabit Comcast it's
this damn stream speed is decent but in
his fun room I agree I have a big
American flag on the wall which I would
show you if I had a mirror that's over
there oh yeah let's go only make it rain
can I buy things already at the store oh
yes oh free oh I love free health
potions about one of those
okay all right let's go go on top but
we're on the other side how do you go
top on the other side wait should I not
be here let's go
you're lagging you have such a good
computer oh yeah let's get him he's out
I'm gonna call another Tower don't worry
because I was just snipe minions and get
kills and now to play this game
wait you're moving oh we're gonna go
bottom okay let's go bottom can we kill
we creep kill wait look at these people
we got to help them
oh yeah your money
so someone killed our people already was
it the guy with the bad computer Oh is
there a turtle can I kill it I can't
kill the turtle okay I'm coming don't
worry I got your back yeah make it rain
oh I made it right on the minions but
just two of them you got a heal bro I'm
gonna heal you I'll heal you got ya oh
you're welcome
I have them here to support
oh yeah make it rain on the enemies yeah
so good rock dude 69 love this game
should we try to kill that guy let me
know what I should do something
yeah died I died I died yeah try run
away
you want to stay here but what if they
come for our turret Oh perfect yeah no
don't worry I'll go go mid bro you're
dead bro you come near my turret again
I need more Manas wait he can make it
rain - oh the other one I had was much
prettier before you know I had Kate
before she was she not that complicated
yeah I know that's why I didn't like her
but she was prettier than this one no
this one's ok because I can make it rain
but I don't have enough mana anymore no
I like girls who are pretty dresses oh
don't worry I got you wait how do I get
more mana
how do i what why would I do that should
I go home and buy things at the store
should I go home and no 600 but it'll
take me a long time to get back I'm
going home oh we know there's all these
people here never might not help
wait no no they almost killed me I got
to go home is it worth it to run or
recall really but what if I'm really
close to home oh yeah
what should I buy boots of speed that's
all I can afford I can buy another
dorians blade oh now I have two Dorian's
blades Oh sick love stacked I'm good at
this game right yeah
[Applause]
can I use lots of mana now could I buy
more mana with real money I'll spend
real money on mana but so I shouldn't
make it rain on these minions but it's
gonna be so satisfying what'd I do
oh that was so satisfying that was so
satisfying though
look at all these minions I can make it
rain on them that's so satisfying that
won't use queue attack on them don't
worry I will use queue attack on this
guy though that wasn't you who died
right
oh no we're good yeah I know I got him
Oh get him get him bro I'll make it rain
on these minions no no no no no no oh
God them did you die oh sweet does he
get money oh that's a good deal yeah I'm
gonna kill their tower no I'll make it
rain on you bro
should I goos my how are their jar they
showing up I haven't died yet I'm
invincible
our teammates suck why we get partnered
with noobs I've never played before but
I'm not an idiot really did they buy
things in the store you have to do that
it's an important part of the tutorial
Oh take our guys I don't know how to use
our wait let's kill this guy alright
alright
oh good I love satisfying ours
can I go kill turtle now sweet I'm going
to kill turtle
I hate turtle
I attacked a plant oh sorry what I don't
have it our he's new don't worry oh no
I'm gonna die I'm running who an orb you
died oh my god you should have told me
yeah I'm a beast of this game I'm gonna
stop a ball I'm running home oh wait I
shouldn't have run home I should have
recalled home and then oh my god they
got 17 kills versus four of ours why'd I
get noobs on my team
press B what's B oh I don't wanna do
that I'm already here I ran home you
have to kill minions with the last hit
to get gold
I'm coming I'm about to make a rant on
the minions no I didn't buy any ours
okay you promise me it's easy to use
it's not like Kate I love make it rain
it's my favorite ability
okay all right now should I use it yeah
wait why oh it sucked it sucked
died help me kill him got him I'm so
good at this game
oh I hate when my minions get the last
hit on minions then I don't get gold
that wasn't you right there should be
better at this game I don't have any
mana how do i Rico beat that's what I
wanted
you have to stay still I understand I
will stay still next time I use my R I
can't even buy anymore shit
now I have all my mana back wait we need
to go defend up top did they knock our
tower down that's terrible
oh don't worry I'm coming to kill that
guy my R is almost recharged
oh yeah ah wait I'm nearsighted let's
just hang out by the tower tower
super-safe
were you leaving me here bro oh he was
killing you I didn't realize that
wait they killed me too how'd they do
that I didn't even get a chance to use
my attack
oh what a cheater
those guys hacking
what we're gonna lose our way
and remember money to buy things oh yeah
let's kill this guy
let's hack it you can't do that
we don't have anymore towers they all
went mid people on the bottom did great
I'm gonna go farm creep or whatever that
means
no no let's kill him
nice nice I'm killing this thing where I
cancel my or again I'm so bad at using
that oh yeah was that worth it for all
that matter probably not oh my god
why does my teammate so bad
No
oh I lost don't use our against monsters
yeah I think this that makes sense why
are people all noobs what wait you're
telling me that there's people on our
team trying to lose
so these are like gold farmers
nice can we reconstruct our things so
the super minions will stop that's cool
yes right now I can buy good things Oh
rapid firecannon all that thing looks
good yeah that our was good I know
don't kill my tower yeah yeah yeah
you're trying to run away bro trying to
run away that's right
Oh oh that guy's a high-level I missed
good my arse back
Oh how'd they get that thing Wow well I
should use my are on it
dad
Jiji
we're all the dentists next week guys
and excited I found out that you could
for free
get them to clean your teeth well I have
health insurance and it's a scam and you
gotta use it because otherwise the
insurance company makes money all right
how about have we lose I played so well
do I get Ilan for that oh boy I leveled
up I'm three now let's play again
all right fix my audio explain to me
what you want me to do here's my audio
I tried
all right no how do I go back and see
how I did it that game
Manchester
five hundred fifty thousand are you
running these in cloud downstairs Oh
overview yeah that was a sad game Oh
perfect let's go
okay nano danger is a subscriber and he
says the audio is fine so you know what
it's fine you tell me to fix my audio I
have no idea what you want me to do
yeah no now I'm gamer I play League of
Legends I am League of Legends stream
right now audio is fine
Bruce your bro oh yeah I know which one
I'm gonna be wait I can't be Miss
Fortune know who's Riven she looks
pretty who else can make it rain wait
what else do I do
what do I do uh take Tristana that's the
only non-complicated 100 she looks
terrible though
oh she looks like a purple Shrek
yeah I'm just saying your guy wasn't
much to look at but I don't understand
what you say you can't hear anything
what do you mean do you need me to add a
new source audio output capture create
new like that I don't think that worked
like that like that like that
that didn't work
[Music]
audios fine okay I don't know bro you
guys fix your computer wait
but vector Slayer took my hero
I bought misfortune to get a refund oh I
didn't even know have you know have you
seen how much better our computers are
than everybody else's what I do is fun
you know what let me ban this guy I
would ban you if you twitch is that a
thing
only when they lie audio sounds loud you
for me but I've got a lot of intensive
software on a crappy pc so I'm guessing
it's me bro the bike computer good
computer I bought I have this Mac as
2017 Mac I didn't by 2018 Mac I have 27
twitchy's now yeah yeah they liked my
League of Legends skill guys how's my
League of Legends skill am I good at
this game
thank you subscribers then I don't know
if there's a crown me more subscribers
only if you watch replays everybody can
watch normal yeah scamming twit yeah
that's a good point
no they hold it for like 14 days but
YouTube will let you do that forever so
what you just upload gigabytes and
gigabytes of random videos to YouTube no
cuz they still get copyright screened no
it's twitch prime does that mean I'm
getting money what does that mean you
just pay twitch money because you guys
know that the only reason I stream on
Twitch is to make money I made one
hundred and thirty two dollars last
twitch payment cycle I think it was
actually sent to my bank account yeah
Nick Nick he Lowell are you actually
audio is only for subscribers you have
to subscribe how are you twitch Brown
without pay can i research brain without
pay you have an Amazon account oh oh oh
Amazon Prime Wow alright let's play wait
I don't know which which which ability
to I spam
I hate all these ability no that
involves thinking I want make it rain I
can't even buy sword all I can buy his
shitty shield
I bought shield oh wait I almost didn't
buy free thing all right which which
Lane are we going
let's go top I hate this champion
I wanted to play Miss Fortune Amazon
bought twitch oh yeah I did know that it
really occurred to me the rich get
richer
oh yeah let's kill him
I'm coming I'm coming I'm coming why no
cheater if I had rocket jump I could
have killed him
I picked wrong
that ability sucks II
is the worst
I did it on the enemy Oh see I mrs.
heroes I miss misfortune I'll level up
that's right I'm getting double use how
is he healing
Oh
that sounds cool if I was good at this
game how about if I kill a minion boom
oh wow 21 cooldown that sucks
even though I killed a bunch of minions
Nicola you suck you're bad for my twitch
channel wine one of our guys died
already
w w's my new favorite yeah die that's
right could we go kill turtle
boom die oh wait now he's gonna kill me
he's gonna kill me
and now I don't have matter anymore
where are you oh I don't have any life
dying yeah without
boom
but I can't I don't have any mana or
health oh but look at all those crunchy
minions with those last kill easy to get
Oh
we can get this guy if we both rocket
jump at the same time
yeah let's just hang out in there and
then when he comes by let's ambush oh we
got a plan
wait for him to come by ambush him what
happened so did mine yeah but we died
oh my internet lagged uh we put my
internet lagged that was so shitty
someone ddosed me from buying boots of
speed you know what probably people
uploaded stuff on comma thank you thank
you surrender thank you please subscribe
to my channel I give me money I only do
twitch so I can make money did we go top
again wow if Majan that didn't lag we
just would have killed him and got away
did you see the hackers bullshit
I'm a great League of Legends player
there's no way I would have died
I still have to walk all the way back
how come ginger fucker has a six now
also he gets all the XP that's cheating
can I have a lane to myself there's
another person cogmed down
oh no oh no I'm dying I'm dying okay
what
nope nope
dead
where are you
nice
see but he's a level 8 and I'm only a
level 5 it's not fair
I thought all people were equal
what does it do how do I use it oh yeah
I did oh I got him yeah that's right
dude never stood a chance he shouldn't
have messed with rock dude 69
we're gonna take down his tower
oh there's a hero
we can take them
nice got him got him got him he's weak
he's weak ease we calm down yeah do I
get life for that sweet I'm gold now
pickaxe what we're doing better this
game sweet I hate having to walk back
though oh they need help on mid
now come nobody talks anymore
yeah
on my alternates back
my ultimate is great do we take that
tower down
nice
you want to kill that hero I'll come
join you what yeah get him
he won't see shit he's a noob he told me
get him
oh we can teleport a cheater oh let's
take away his mana let's take away his
mana take my cue I think my cue socks I
still don't understand how my e works
oh my e is very complicated oh but I
have an R again oh my god there's two of
them where should we go okay I'm coming
Oh we kill the thingy
they got them oh here's a guy
nice you got them I need to go heal
you put the e on the enemy than the more
you attack the more damage it'll do okay
I understand
I seem body thing heal heal heal heal
heal heal
I wish should we go
and no one's going top I'm going to top
to level up on these minions
I understand my okay it's pretty good
got the tower
boom yeah who said I shouldn't use all
those spells that's right
too close to tower
all rush top
dye minions oh oh yeah yeah no house
doing so well I've gold now though bf
sword that's right and we serve wrath
it's probably a ripoff just like if you
spend your money I know how capitalism
works
wait but there's a hero up top you want
to rush him oh I think someone's coming
for him pyre of strike Oh Papa scope is
you can't read playboy I just oh you got
him nice nice legendary I heard I was
legendary and then I died but legendary
I mean I got one kill I have my are
attack back though
oh no we're crushing it especially we
take down this tower easy easy I want
one of them buttons that's right
wait no nobody come back when you're
hanging out here you want to get those
guys I can use my are attack
nice wait no there's still two of them
no no they're coming for me to cover for
me help oh I can put ye on Atari that's
pretty cool
that's what it says yeah oh they got you
man I watched that I can click for death
recap wow they must have got a lot of
gold from you
oh good thing I'm buying a guardian
angel wait I should have bought infinity
edge
I'll have bought the wrong items that
sounded like a ripoff why'd I buy that
that sounds good no don't worry I have
spells I just killed seven minions with
one spell I'm unstoppable no I should
have died a bunch of times at this I
feel bad I'm a bad teammate
no oh that was you
scared the enemies killed a dragon why
don't we kill a dragon
oh here's a guy
oh they're all here I want in on this
nice I get something
oh yes oh this is oh look at a sleigh
I put my thing on the turret oh I love
this push
oh yeah we're crushing it oh this is
gonna make super shets
oh yeah where is it I can't see hang on
should I go somewhere
yeah we'll kill the worm what if it
kills us
all right I'm here are you here
why Oh try and forget that I got a I
gotta go help these people out don't
worry I'm gonna kill random Rhino with
my with my are attack shit
how is just resurrect Oh guardian angels
the best oh I love guardian angel it
saved me I would have died this is the
battle no shit
all right now I'm dead can I go yeah oh
I can undo in the shop while I was still
in base I shouldn't have bought stupid
guardian angel let it know that
the spawn time so long can I sell my
guardian angel I bought a second door on
shield
I bought a third door on she cult oh
yeah
combined my guardian angel and my three
door on shields I'm unstoppable
Oh DNF yeah I know what is d exhausts
target champion I know F I used f once
that's like guardian angel but not as
good oh that's right they're all hanging
out in base
the worm let's go
nice that looks useful
oh yeah the worms attacking me help
wait yeah that was a scam I wasted all
my attacks on that why'd we attack the
woman who's dumb
they have the turtle so it's hard to do
the warm that makes sense I'm killing
this guy nice
where our super minions
oh yeah I'm hanging out with this super
minion
is he here's a doctor
on with daylight dreary yeah oh we have
good teammates this time we get this guy
no he killed my friend
he killed us both
and through his shields of Doran I
something couldn't kill me
we do win though right
with your Crispo came back cheaters
yeah I'm hungry guys you know okay
I didn't even get to use my our attack
psychic I'm going that way
look at that micro guys
yeah
Wow Wow
how come they get to kill dragons and we
don't we tried to kill a worm and we
lost oh oh I'm dead no nope I have
guardian angel
[Music]
yeah but I bought guardian angel
I like this hero though these are cool
abilities oh we're starting to lose
again
wait what this guy in the middle is so
weak
what giggling
oh the gays
gays are very strong and that make sense
he's running he's running nice should we
kill this worm how come they got to kill
dragon why should we just lose
what if we kill him
he doesn't die well what if we all gang
up on we're not good at that what I have
a Q ability Oh Q no no it's like
teleporting guy I'm dead I can kill bear
in one view what is that a trump well
Ally super minions that's good we're
winning again oh I can kill this guy
this guy's only 11 oh you got him I have
2,000 gold can i buy something oh yes
Lord Dominic's regards yeah I don't know
I wanna buy guardian angel I'm in such
bad purchasing decisions early on in my
life
don't get him didn't go below bow get
him I saw him he was almost dead
let's go kill gingko biloba well if we
all gang up on it oh here here let's go
kill baron no okay okay
kill the inhibitor I'm on it
oh look oh we're all together oh I love
this teamwork
up
oh my god I got away oh no never mind
the gay guy just teleported ah look at
all these minions here that's so much
minion gold I can get
yeah the gay guy is not fair we're
losing now aren't we
he shouldn't be in this new bleep oh my
god they're here they're gonna kill our
thing and now they get super minions
they're in our base
don't worry guardian angels got me
but we lost oh we have people in the
base that's crazy
no but they get super minions now it's
not fair
signals that enemies are missing
why don't we ever do dragon
who got dragon we have dragon oh nice
love when we get dragon yeah dragon I
feel invincible
oh it's gingko biloba we got to run but
there's all of us here can we all
together kill gingko biloba
I died kill them oh you're gonna get him
you're gonna get gingko biloba oh we got
away
where'd he go
Oh ginkgo biloba press tab four stacks
oh sweet am i losing
I am a man
wait how am i dad again I mean my base
Oh stupid well at least I didn't die for
nothing are we winning again this games
long guys
I can't believe I bought a guardian
angel
where is it he's in our base kill ginkgo
biloba Wow he you like one shots me GG
what
I'm done with this game cell door and
shield and buy a bf sword are we lost
all right guys I've learned that I'm not
cut out to be illegal in the stream room
Wow you know everybody is things are
good at in life bye bye twitchy's thank
you please like and subscribe so I will
keep creating all this great content for
you it's the like button down there it's
the easiest thing you could do to help
out it's also sign up for things that
like give me twitch money bro you know
there's no foodies bedtime goodnight
which is yeah switch money that's right
all right ladies